Guide to the Jake Austen Zine Collection 1972-2013
University of Chicago Library
- Greenberger, David, The duplex planet, 178, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Greenberger, David, The duplex planet, 179, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Greenberger, David, The duplex planet, 180, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Greenberger, David, The duplex planet, 181, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Greenberger, David, The duplex planet, 182, 2008 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Greenberger, David, The duplex planet, 183, 2008 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Greenberger, David, The duplex planet, 184, 2009 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Greenberger, David, The duplex planet, 185, 2009 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Greenberger, David, The duplex planet, 186, 2009 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Forster, F.R. "Russ", 8-track mind magazine, 91, Spring 1997 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Greenberger, David, An exact spectacular, 1994, Has laid in an invitation to exhibit on The Duplex Planet, inscribed to Jake Austen (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Urban guerrilla zine, 10.5, undated (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Dwelling portably, April 2001 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Dwelling portably, 5, April 2010 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Rock, Craven, Eaves of ass, 6 - The music issue, undated (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Rock, Craven, Eaves of ass, 7 - Promise and theft, undated (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Frederickston, Eddie, "Eddie says…."millennium calender" [!], 2000 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Sparrow, T. Edward III (editor-in-chief), "El diablo, el amigo, undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Eleventh pin, 2, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Elk, 5, January 2004, Inscribed "#92 J.W." (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Elk, 6, March 2004 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Linna, Miriam, El loco, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Edelstein, Johny, Engelbert Humperdinck, 2, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Edelstein, Johny, Engelbert Humperdinck, 3, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Kelly, Dan (editor), Evil, 6, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Kelly, Dan (editor), Evil, 7, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Alexander, Yale, Evil, 5, August 1992 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Wolbert, Wayne Alejandro, Existe, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Taylor, Dan, Exploitation retrospect, 36, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Taylor, Dan, Exploitation retrospect, 37, March 1993 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Taylor, Dan, Exploitation retrospect, 38, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Taylor, Dan, Exploitation retrospect, 39, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Taylor, Dan, Exploitation retrospect, 40, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Taylor, Dan, Exploitation retrospect, 43, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Crosby, Lisa (editor), Eye, July/August 1999 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Crosby, Lisa (editor), Eye, September/October 1999 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Crosby, Lisa (editor), Eye, November/December 1999 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Snyder, Phil; Amann, Gina, Eyewash, 3, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Snyder, Phil; Amann, Gina, Eyewash, 4, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Snyder, Phil; Amann, Gina, Eyewash, 5, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Friedman, R. Seth (publisher), Factsheet five, 47, undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Friedman, R. Seth (publisher), Factsheet five, 52, July? 1994 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Friedman, R. Seth (publisher), Factsheet five, 53, October? 1994 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Friedman, R. Seth (publisher), Factsheet five, 63, February? 1998 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Friedman, R. Seth (publisher), Factsheet five, 64, June? 1998 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Walker, Keith; Walker, Rosemary, Fanzine fanatique quarterly, Fall 2000 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Lee, Brandi, Fat grrrly, 2, December 2008 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Spangler, Tina, Femme flicke, 1, Summer 1993, Has handwritten note from the author laid in (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Spangler, Tina, Femme flicke, 2, 1994?, Has handwritten note from the author laid in (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Spangler, Tina, Femme flicke, 6, undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Roth, Larry I. (editor), 1544 West Grace newsletter, "vol. 1, no. 3-4, Spring/Summer 1995 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Roth, Larry I. (editor), 1544 West Grace newsletter, "vol. 2, no. 1, Fall/Autumn 1995 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Roth, Larry I. (editor), 1544 West Grace newsletter, "vol. 2, no. 2, Winter 1996 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Roth, Larry I. (editor), 1544 West Grace newsletter, "vol. 2, no. 3, Spring 1996 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Roth, Larry I. (editor), 1544 West Grace newsletter, "vol. 3, no. 1, Autumn 1996 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Roth, Larry I. (editor), 1544 West Grace newsletter, "vol. 3, no. 1, issue 10, February 1997 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Rhonda; Tamara, Fight like a girl, 2, Fall 1996 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Rayson, Anthony, Fight the white, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Fisher, Dave, Filler, 7, December 1997 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Fisher, Dave, Filler, 8, June 1998 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Bruce, Scott, Flake: the breakfast nostalgia magazine, 10, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Bruce, Scott, Flake: the breakfast nostalgia magazine, 11, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Yeti, Greg A. R. (editor), The flashing astonisher, 9, undated (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Yeti, Greg A. R. (editor), The flashing astonisher, 10, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Yeti, Greg A. R. (editor), The flashing astonisher, 10.5, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Yeti, Greg A. R. (editor), The flashing astonisher, 11, Spring 1998 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Flash!, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Colebank, Shannon, Flashpoint, 3 - Documenting the fact AIDS does not exist, January 2000 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Davis, Jaina A. (editor), Flatter!, 3, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Davis, Jaina A. (editor), Flatter!, 6, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Davis, Jaina A. (editor), Flatter!, 7, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Davis, Jaina A. (editor), Flatter!, 8, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Davis, Jaina A. (editor), Flatter!, 9, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Flip, 2004? (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Helt, Keith, Flotation device, 4, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Sanchez, John (editor), Flying buttress, 3, undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Agnish, Jai (editor), Flygirl, 8, undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Foodbox, 4, 1993? (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Kresovich, Brant, For the clerisy, 11, November 1994 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- 442ème rue, 67, July 2006 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- 442ème rue, 73, August 2007 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- 442ème rue, 81, October 2008 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Johnson, Matthew, Freak tension, 10, April 2004 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Johnson, Matthew, Freak tension, 11, August 2004 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Johnson, Matthew, Freak tension, 12, January 2005 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Free agent, 5, Fall 1998 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Theresa, Free popcorn, 1, March 1994 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Front porch, 72, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Rimkus, Kyle, Full frontal nudity, 1, June 1994 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Rimkus, Kyle, Full frontal nudity, 2, November 1994 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Rimkus, Kyle, Full frontal nudity, 3, June 1995 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Labrat, Eric, Genuine rocket pack, undated (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Kuhlmann, Sam (editor); Hume, Andrew (editor), Fran magazine, "vol. 2, no. 3, May/June 2004 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Kuhlmann, Sam (editor); Hume, Andrew (editor), Fran magazine, "vol. 2, no. 4, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Kuhlmann, Sam (editor); Hume, Andrew (editor), Fran magazine, "vol. 3, no. 1, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- F.R.A.Y. newsletter, "vol. 1, no. 2, September 1995 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Moscato, Marc, Generation latex, 5, undated, Has bound in Doodles-n-Diddles with Julie and Robin, issue 3 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- David, Jacob, "George Bush, Jr. = stupid rich nitwit, or, Nero fiddled while Rome burned, July 2002 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Carlile, Jennifer; Fox, Kirsten, Get out your dictionary, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Get well, undated (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Rogovin, Al (editor), Girder, 1, undated (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Rogovin, Al (editor), Girder, 2, undated (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Nelson, Bob (editor), Giants and little people in fact and fiction, 1, undated (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Nelson, Bob (editor), Giants and little people in fact and fiction, 2, Winter 1995 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Nelson, Bob (editor), Giants and little people in fact and fiction, 3, Spring 1996 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Nelson, Bob (editor), Giants and little people in fact and fiction, 4, Spring 1996 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Nelson, Bob (editor), Giants and little people in fact and fiction, 5, Summer 1996 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Nelson, Bob (editor), Giants and little people in fact and fiction, 6, Fall 1996, Inscribed by the author to Jake Austen (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Nelson, Bob (editor), Giants and little people in fact and fiction, 7, Winter 1996/1997 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Nakamura, Eric (editor, publisher); Wong, Martin (editor), Giant robot, 4, Winter/Spring 1996 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Nakamura, Eric (editor, publisher); Wong, Martin (editor), Giant robot, 5, Summer 1996 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Nakamura, Eric (editor, publisher); Wong, Martin (editor), Giant robot, 6, Winter 1996 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Nakamura, Eric (editor, publisher); Wong, Martin (editor), Giant robot, 7, Spring 1997 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Nakamura, Eric (editor, publisher); Wong, Martin (editor), Giant robot, 11, Summer 1998 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Nakamura, Eric (editor, publisher); Wong, Martin (editor), Giant robot, 39, Spring 2005 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Nakamura, Eric (editor, publisher); Wong, Martin (editor), Giant robot, 40, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Nakamura, Eric (editor, publisher); Wong, Martin (editor), Giant robot, 43, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Nakamura, Eric (editor, publisher); Wong, Martin (editor), Giant robot, 44, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Nakamura, Eric (editor, publisher); Wong, Martin (editor), Giant robot, 45, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Nakamura, Eric (editor, publisher); Wong, Martin (editor), Giant robot, 52, 2008 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Cheetah, Rita (writer); Xen, Rv. (illustrator), Glam bang pow!, undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Puss, Glamour, Glamour, Bring back glamour, May 1999 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Puss, Glamour, Glamour, "Meet our newest, most glamorous columnist inside - Jayne Mansfield, undated (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Puss, Glamour, Glamour, "What is this thing called "beefcake"?, undated (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Puss, Glamour, Glamour, "["Exotic"], undated (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Reilly, Daniel, Glitter, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Edelstein, Johny, Gnare, 1994, Inscribed by the author to Jake Austen (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Go, 5, Fall 2000 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Go metric, 1, Spring 1995, Inscribed to Jake Austen by staff member Mike Faloon (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Go metric, 2, Summer 1995 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Go metric, 3, Fall 1995 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Go metric, 5, Spring 1996 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Go metric, 7, Winter 1997 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Sheldrake, Terry (editor), Go metric, 8, Fall 1997 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Sheldrake, Terry (editor), Go metric, 9, Spring 1998 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Go metric, 11, Summer 1999 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Sheldrake, Terry (editor), Go metric, 12, Summer 2000 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Sheldrake, Terry (editor), Go metric, 13, Spring 2001 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Sheldrake, Terry (editor), Go metric, 14, Fall 2001 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Sheldrake, Terry (editor), Go metric, 15, Spring 2002 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Go metric, 16, Winter 2002/2003 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Go metric, 17, Fall 2003 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Sheldrake, Terry (publisher); Faloon, Mike (editor), Go metric, 18, Spring 2004 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Sheldrake, Terry (publisher); Faloon, Mike (editor), Go metric, 19, Winter 2005 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Sheldrake, Terry (publisher); Faloon, Mike (editor), Go metric, 21, undated (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Sheldrake, Terry (publisher); Faloon, Mike (editor), Go metric, 22, undated (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Hammer, Jon; McBurnie, Karen, The goofball's almanak, 1997, Inscribed by the authors to Jake Austen (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Diamond, Mike (editor); Jenkins, Andy (editor); Jonze, Spike (editor); Horovitz, Adam (editor); Mack, Bob (editor); Tremaine, Jeff (editor); Yauch, Adam (editor), Grand royal, Fall/Winter 1993 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Cassini, Tina; Una, Cristina, Gravee, "vol. 1, no. 1, undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Cassini, Tina; Una, Cristina, Gravee, 2, Winter 1995 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Cassini, Tina; Una, Cristina, Gravee, 3, Summer 1995 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Cassini, Tina; Una, Cristina, Gravee, 4, undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Cassini, Tina; Una, Cristina, Gravee, 5, undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Road, Cristy C., Greenzine, 14, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Zobel, Gregory, Gregory Zobel's mental health advisory, 1, November 2000 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Grey city journal, "Friday, October 29, 1993" (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Lennard, Dann, Grunted warning, 13, October 2011 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- A guide to picking locks, 2, undated (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Ramadasha, Gunk, 4, undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Stevens, Andy (editor), Gulp, 5, Early Winter 1993 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Edelstein, Johny, Hacksaw off your face, 1, April 1994 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Edelstein, Johny, Hacksaw off your face, 2, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Haddock, October 2005 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Simplot, Jason, Happy goat, 9, Summer 2000 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Weinman, Paul, Hardball ain't all bucolic, 1986, SAMISDAT, vol.45, no.3 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Hoflich, Peter, Head cheese Japan, 2002, Has handwritten letter from the author to Jake Austen and three Japanese advertisements laid in (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Gnade, Adam, The heat and the hot earth: a novella, December 2011, First edition of 1,000 copies (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Marzano, Mary Beth, Hey, 3, Summer 1994 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Marzano, Mary Beth, Hey, 4, undated (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Marzano, Mary Beth, Hey, 6, undated (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Marzano, Mary Beth, Hey, 8, undated (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Marzano, Mary Beth, Hey, 13, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Marzano, Mary Beth, Hey, 15, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Palmer, Andrew, Hipsters quarterly review, "15 - Special "platinum hair black at the roots" issue, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Meschino, Steven, Hodge podge, "vol. 1, no. 2, undated, Has two handwritten letters from the author laid in, one addressed to Jake Austen and dated August 26, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Larry-bob, Holy titclamps, 15, September 1995 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Briggs, Raleigh, How to make soap without burning your face off, 2009 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Goodrich, Sebastian; Goodrich, Miles, Hungry freaks, 3, Spring 1996 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Goodrich, Sebastian; Goodrich, Miles, Hungry freaks, 4, September 1996 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Goodrich, Sebastian; Goodrich, Miles, Hungry freaks, 5, Summer 1997 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Edelstein, Johny, Ice cream and cheese, "vol. 1, no. 2, November 1993, Inscribed by the author to Jake Austen, dated November 1993 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- I didn't do this to impress you, undated (Box 14, Folder 7)
- K., Amy, If Prince was my girlfriend, 1, Fall 1997 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Gerken, John, I hate this part of texas, 5, January 2006 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Mazer, Craig (editor), Impact, 49, February/March 2004 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Ninj, Infiltration, 15 - Infiltration at sea!, January 2000 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Leon, Harmon, The institute of blinding light: catalog of sacred items, undated (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Livingstone, John, Insight, 2 - Sophomore slump issue, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Thompson, Bob, International playboy zine, 3, undated (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Binty, Tony, Inty-binty, 16, 1996? (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Cizek, Jennifer, Ironic flem, May 1998 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- It's yours, 3, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Japankore, 6, August 1995 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Gnade, Adam, Hey hey lonesome: a novella, 4, October 2011 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Masters, Jack, Jack, 1, Early 2002 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Janelle; Jeff, Jank, 10, January/February 1998 (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Janelle; Jeff, Jank, 13, May 1998 (Box 14, Folder 21)
- De Rose, Steve, Japan jaunt, "vol. 1, no. 1, March 2013 (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Hughes, Scott, The Jay Robinson newsletter, 1, October 1992 (Box 14, Folder 23)
- Hughes, Scott; Martinak, Joe, The Jay Robinson newsletter, 2, January 1993 (Box 14, Folder 23)
- Hughes, Scott; Martinak, Joe, The Jay Robinson newsletter, 3, October 1993 (Box 14, Folder 23)
- Hughes, Scott; Martinak, Joe, The Jay Robinson newsletter, 4, September 1994 (Box 14, Folder 23)
- Farseth, Erik, The J. cruelty catalog, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 24)
- Farseth, Erik, The J. cruelty catalog, 10, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 24)
- Rodriguez, Alejandro; Montelongo, Alejandro X.; Jiffy; Alvarez, Elizabeth, Jify, undated (Box 14, Folder 25)
- Liebowitz, David (publisher), Jinx, 4, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 26)
- Liebowitz, David (editor-in-chief); Ibdeyo (editor-in-chief), Jinx, 5, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 26)
- Dawson, James N., JND pseudo zine, 8, August 2000 (Box 14, Folder 27)
- Hughes, Scott (club president), The John Agar fan club, 1, January 1995 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Hughes, Scott (club president), The John Agar fan club, 2, Summer 1995 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Hughes, Scott (club president), The John Agar fan club, 3, Winter 1996 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Hughes, Scott (club president), The John Agar fan club, 4, Summer 1996 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Hughes, Scott (club president), The John Agar fan club, 5, Winter 1997 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Hughes, Scott (club president), The John Agar fan club, 6, Summer 1997 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Hughes, Scott (club president), The John Agar fan club, 7, Winter/Spring 1998 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Hughes, Scott (club president), The John Agar fan club, 8, Summer/Fall 1998 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Hughes, Scott (club president), The John Agar fan club, 9, Winter/Spring 1999 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Hughes, Scott (club president), The John Agar fan club, 10, Winter 2000 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Hughes, Scott (club president), The John Agar fan club, 11, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Hughes, Scott (club president), The John Agar fan club, 12, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Junk, 3, undated (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Boehmer, Bill, Johnny on the spot, 8, 1992? (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Howland, Dan, The journal of ride theory, The time-travelers' guidebook to 20th century world's fairs, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Gevurtz, Steve, Journalsong, 6, undated (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Hughes, Scott (club president), The June Wilkinson fan club, 1, Spring 1997 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Hughes, Scott (club president), The June Wilkinson fan club, 2, Fall/Winter 1997 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Hughes, Scott (club president), The June Wilkinson fan club, 3, Spring/Summer 1998 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Hughes, Scott (club president), The June Wilkinson fan club, 4, Fall/Winter 1998/1999 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Hughes, Scott (club president), The June Wilkinson fan club, 5, Spring/Summer 1999 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Hughes, Scott (club president), The June Wilkinson fan club, 6, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Hughes, Scott (club president), The June Wilkinson fan club, 7, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Hughes, Scott (club president), The June Wilkinson fan club, 8, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Weinman, Paul, Just because I didn't leave the driving to us I got jailed and juiced good, undated (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Lennard, Dann; Vnuk, Helen, Keeping up with Jones, 1, Spring 2008 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Lennard, Dann; Vnuk, Helen, Keeping up with Jones, 2, Spring 2009 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Lennard, Dann; Vnuk, Helen, Keeping up with Jones, 4, Spring 2011 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Amico, Hope; Gerken, John, Keep fighting Texas, 7, 2007, This title is a splicing of Keep Loving, Keep Fighting 7 and I Hate This Part of Texas 7 - colophon (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Wagner, Jessica; Jenkins, Sassafras, Kitchen Amerika, 2007 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Robbins, Randy, Kitten mittens, 1, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Nudd, Paul, Klustercrust, 2007 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- "Kool man: the amazing story of Robert Dupree, the king of oral love, undated (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Dickinson, James Luther, Kreature comforts: low-life guide to Memphis, 4th edition, undated (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Dickinson, James Luther, Kreature comforts: low-life guide to Memphis, 5th revised edition, undated (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Coon, Ralph, The last prom: electic esoterica for a better tomorrow, 1, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Learning good consent, undated (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Leighton, Rodney, The Leighton look, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- "Leland Homer Rayson, August 23, 1921-January 8, 2001, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Wilms, Kris; Wilms, Tom, L'Entrepot, 4, undated (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Bastian, Danielle, Liar, 2, September 1993 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- Libel, Jenna, Libel, 1, undated (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Libel, Jenna, Libel, 4, undated (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Libel, Jenna, Libel, 6, undated (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Libel, Jenna, Libel, 7, undated, Inscribed by the author to Jake Austen (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Libel, Jenna, Libel, 9, undated (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Limp, 2, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- This little Sicilian, undated (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Grauer, Yael, Live beat, 3, undated, Inscribed by the author to Jake Austen (Box 16, Folder 3)
- The lowbrow reader of basement brow comedy, 3, Summer 2003 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- The lowbrow reader of basement brow comedy, 4, Fall 2004 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- The lowbrow reader of basement brow comedy, 5, Summer 2006 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- The lowbrow reader of basement brow comedy, 6, Summer 2008 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- The lowbrow reader of basement brow comedy, 8, Fall 2010/Winter 2011 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- M.A.C.E., undated (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Bogard, Seth, Mac and me, 2, undated (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Perkins, Helena, Madwoman, 5, January 1994 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Perkins, Helena, Madwoman, 7, June 1995 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Perkins, Helena, Madwoman, 8, July 1996 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Perkins, Helena, Madwoman, 9, December 1997 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Perkins, Helena, Madwoman, 10, September 1998 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Wrekk, Alex, Stolen sharpie revolution: a DIY zine resource, undated (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Weldon, Michael J. (editor), Psychotronic, 24, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Flores, Michael (editor), It's only a movie!, 1, April/May 1990 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Male, "vol. 22, no. 11, November 1972 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Kendall, Lukas, Film score monthly, 48, August 1994 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Leavold, Andrew (editor), Trash confidential, 1, August 1998 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Trash confidential, 2, September 1998 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Paxton, Timothy (editor), Monster!, "vol. 4, no. 4, issue 76, April 1992 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Wandromedia, 5, undated (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Biel, Joe, Bamboozled: The Joey Torrey story, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Bektashi, Muhammad A., Malcolm X: some questions answered, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- Poff, Kyle; Freimuth, Michael, Matériel, 1, Winter 2009 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Maxine: a literate companion for churlish girls and rakish women, 3, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Oberc, Larry; Weinman, Paula, May your bullet enter my mouth, undated (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Meyer, Herbie; Meyer, Christoph (editor), Mean zine submarine, undated (Box 16, Folder 21)
- Media junky, 14, Winter 2010 (Box 16, Folder 22)
- Media junky, 18, Winter 2013 (Box 16, Folder 22)
- Stylites, Simeon (editor); Malatesta, Margana (editor), Meshuggah: oddball fiction and subversive thought, 6, December 1992 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Metamagic media catalog, undated, Has laid in an advertisement for metamagic.org/strange and a parody dollar bill (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Kwok, De (editor), Milky, 7, undated (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Gottfried, Ted R., Modern monument, Premiere issue, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Moral suckling, undated (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Pembleton, Lee, Mom, 4, undated (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Pembleton, Lee, Mom, 6, undated (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Pembleton, Lee, Mom, 7, undated (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Pembleton, Lee, Mom, 8, undated (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Pembleton, Lee, Mom, 9, undated (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Monarch, 1, 2011 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Pescetelli, Claudio; Milazzo, Annalisa, Mondo capellone, 7, undated (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Admiral Andrew, Monkeybite, 1, January 1997 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Mothers news, Lists issue, February 2012 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Mothers news, Special edition - frogs, undated (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Mothers news, undated (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Walters, Britton (editor), Moo juice megazine, 16, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 11)